virtueplanet.com 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Policies

The VirtuePlanet Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information when you use VirtuePlanet's products and services, including information provided when you use VirtuePlanet. In addition, the following describes our privacy practices that are specific to VirtuePlanet. 

## Personal information 

You need a VirtuePlanet Account to access VirtuePlanet. VirtuePlanet asks for some personal information when you create a VirtuePlanet Account, including your alternate contact information and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A VirtuePlanet Account allows you to access many of our services that require registration. 

VirtuePlanet community, processes and maintains your messages, contact lists and other data related to your account in order to provide the service to you. 

When you use VirtuePlanet, VirtuePlanet's servers automatically record certain information about your use of VirtuePlanet. Similar to other web services, VirtuePlanet records information such as account activity (including storage usage, number of log-ins), data displayed or clicked on (including UI elements, ads, links); and other log information (including browser type, IP-address, date and time of access, cookie ID, and referrer URL). 

## Uses 

VirtuePlanet maintains and processes your VirtuePlanet account and its contents to provide the VirtuePlanet service to you and to improve our services. 

VirtuePlanet's computers process the information in your messages for various purposes, including formatting and displaying the information to you, delivering advertisements and related links, preventing unsolicited bulk email (spam), backing up your messages, and other purposes relating to offering you VirtuePlanet. 

VirtuePlanet may send you information related to your VirtuePlanet account or other VirtuePlanet services. 

## Internet Log 

VirtuePlanet uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The tool uses "cookies," which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' us of the webiste and to compile statistical reports on website activity for VirtuePlanet.com 

We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website. 

## Information sharing and onward transfer 

When you send email, VirtuePlanet includes information such as your email address and the email itself as part of that email. 

We do not sell, rent or otherwise share your personal information with any third parties until and unless we are required to do so by law.
